A Finding Aid to the James Graham & Sons Gallery Records, 1815, 1821, circa 1896-2011, bulk 1950s-1980s, in the Archives of American Art AAA.jamegras
Archives of American Art
- Alphabetical Files, bulk 1955-1986; 1902-1999; circa 1896; Series 1; 15 Linear feet Boxes 1-15
  - Illinois State University, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Indiana State University, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Indonesian Art, 1971-1975 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art (Boston, MA), 1957-1967; 1976 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Institute of Contemporary Art (Washington, D.C.), 1964 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Institute of International Education Benefit (Sept. 1969) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Insurance Policies, 1957-1967; 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Insurance - Thefts, 1955-1971 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Ithaca College, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - J Bills, 1955-1961 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - J Correspondence, 1963-1983 (Box 8, Folder 9-10)
  - J General, 1955-1974 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - [James, Frederic], 1978 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Sidney Janis Gallery, 1969; 1960 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Jemison Gallery, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Jones, Hayden, Appraisal for Mrs. H.C. Menger, 1975-1979 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Joslyn Art Museum, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - K Correspondence, 1957-1988 (Box 8, Folder 17-20)
  - K General, 1955-1976 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Kalamazoo Institute of Arts, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Katonah Gallery, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - [Katz, Paul], 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Kennebec Valley, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Marion Koogler McNay Art Institute, 1975-1977 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Kornblee Gallery, 1969; 1962 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Kraushaar Galleries, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - "Krazy Kat", 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - [Kunin, Myron], 1979-1983 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - L Bills, 1955-1964 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - L Correspondence, 1962-1987 (Box 8, Folder 32-36)
  - L General, 1952-1977 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - La Maison Francaise, Inc., 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Lakeview Center, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Landmark Gallery, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Lauren Rogers Museum, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Legal, James Graham & Sons, Inc., 1979 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Letters [Outgoing Drafts Regarding Artwork], 1960s (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Letters Done for James Graham, 1980-1983 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Letters for James Graham (July 1983- ), 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - [Levine & Levine, C.P.A.'s P.C.], 1980-1983 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Lodge Gallery, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - London, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Longwood College, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Lowe Art Museum, 1971-1975 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - M Bills, 1955-1963 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - M Correspondence, 1963-1985 (Box 9, Folder 7-12)
  - M General, 1967-1977; 1954-1963 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - [Magriel, Paul], 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Malingue, Daniel, 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Adrian Malone and Associates, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Manhattanville College, circa 1950s-1970s (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - [Manoogian, Richard], 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Mass Art Productions, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Maxwell Galleries, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Mc Correspondence, 1962-1983 (Box 9, Folder 21-22)
  - Mc General, 1955-1961; 1967-1977 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Paul McCarron Fine Prints, 1976-1986 (Box 9, Folder 24-25)
  - [McNeil, Robert L., Jr.], 1976-1982 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Medicare/Social Security - Prudential Group Insurance, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Paul Mellon Arts Center, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - The Memorial Gallery, circa 1970s (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - The Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1959-1978 (Box 9, Folder 30-32)
  - [Meyer, Anne Pollack], 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Miami Art Center, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Mid-America Arts Alliance, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Middlebury College, 1957-1973 (Box 9, Folder 36-37)
  - Milwaukee Art Center, 1968; 1975 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - The Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1955-1959; 1968-1975 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous Bills, 1955-1962 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Missouri State Council of the Arts, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Sarah Mleczko Fine Art, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Mollie Bayroff, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - The Montreal Museum of Fine Arts, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Moos Gallery, 1959-1961 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - "Multiples" Exhibition, 1957-1962 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - The Munson Gallery, 1969; 1972 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, 1957-1975 (Box 9, Folder 48-50)
  - Murillo, ["La Anunciacion"], 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - [Murillo, "La Anunciacion"], Chisholm, Hector, 1976-1983 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Museum of the American Indian, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Museum of Arts and Sciences, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Museum of Contemporary Art, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1955-1978 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
  - Museums of Fine Arts, 1968-1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - N Bills, 1955-1963 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - N Correspondence, 1963-1983 (Box 10, Folder 6-10)
  - N General, 1955-1976 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - National Academy of Design, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - [National Academy of Design, Notes on the Financial History, 1826-1863], circa 1896 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - The National Antique and Art Dealers Association of America (NAADAA), 1984-1993 (Box 10, Folder 14-16)
  - The National Art Museum of Sport, 1970-1971; 1962 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - National Gallery of Art, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Neuberger Museum, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - New Jersey State Museum, 1973-1976 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - The New School Art Center, 1968-1970 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - New York City Sales Tax (1955-1963), 1955-1964 (Box 10, Folder 22-25)
  - New York Cultural Center, 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - [New York Foundation for the Arts], 1983 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - New York Historical Society, circa 1950s-1970s (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - New York State Disability (1958-1962), 1958-1963 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - New York State Unemployment (1958-1962), 1956-1962 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - New York State Withholding (1960-1963) (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - New York Studio School, 1964-1969 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - The New York Times, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Newark Museum, 1956-1974 (Box 10, Folder 34-35)
  - Nordfeldt, Emily (B.J.O. Nordfeldt), 1976-1981 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - The North Carolina Museum of Art, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Northern Arizona University Art Gallery, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Northern Illinois University, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Nova Scotia College of Art and Design, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - O Bills, 1955-1961 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - O Correspondence, 1966-1982 (Box 11, Folder 6-8)
  - [O-P Correspondence], 1975-1983 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - O General, 1975-1977; 1953-1966 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Ohio University, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Oklahoma Art Center, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Olana Gallery, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Old World Art Gallery, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Olympia Galleries, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - P Bills (1956-1963), 1954-1963 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - P Correspondence, 1964-1984 (Box 11, Folder 17-21)
  - P General, 1955-1977 (Box 11, Folder 22-23)
  - Paintings, 1956-1959 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Paintings and Drawings Not Yet Stocked, 1957-1962 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Paintings Offered, 1979-1989 (Box 11, Folder 26-28)
  - Paintings Offered and Shown (1991-), 1987-1993 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Paintings Offered That Are of No Interest, 1986-1992 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Reese Palley Gallery, 1969-1973 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Parke-Bernet Galleries, 1956-1966 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Parrish Art Museum, 1969-1975 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Parsons School of Design, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Pending, [Georgia Riley's File?], 1979; 1983-1984 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1957-1968 (Box 11, Folder 36-37)
  - Pennsylvania State University, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Peridot Gallery, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Persian Miniature Show (1963), 1927; 1960-1965 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Personnel, 1966-1974 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1960-1976 (Box 12, Folder 2-5)
  - Ewan Phillips Gallery, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Phoenix Gallery, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Photo Show, 1963-1966 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Photos Out, circa 1969-1971 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Photos Out and Received, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Pitney Bowes, 1950s (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Plaza Art Auction, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Polish Abstract, 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Portraits, circa 1960s-1970s (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Posters Originals, Ltd., 1963-1966 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Press Releases, 1968-early 1990s (Box 12, Folder 16-18)
  - Press Releases [Graham Modern], 1985-1993 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Prints Not Recorded and Print Chron., circa 1980-1984; (8 Smith Corona Microwafers) (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Prospectus, 1957-1959 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Puck Gallery, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Puerto Rican Arts and Cultural Center, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Q Correspondence, 1950s-1960s (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - R Correspondence, 1963-1985 (Box 12, Folder 25-28)
  - R General, 1955-1977 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Rabun, Marc, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Randolph-Macon Women's College, 1972-1976 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Receipts, 1954-1962 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Remenick, Seymour, circa 1960 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Restoration, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Returned Memos, 1983; 1977 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Rhode Island School of Design, circa 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - [Georgia Riley's File?], 1981-1984 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Rittenhouse Gallery, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Rizzoli Gallery, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Roanoke Fine Arts Center, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Robmicka Corp., 1957-1968 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Rochester Memorial Art Gallery, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - University of Rochester Memorial Art Gallery, 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Roof Renovation, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Rosequist Galleries, 1963-1969 (Box 12, Folder 45-46)
  - Royal Academy of Art, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Royal Galleries, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Rubenianum, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - S Bills, 1974-1976; 1955-1964 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - S Correspondence, 1962-1970 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - S Correspondence, 1970-1985 (Box 13, Folder 1-6)
  - S General, 1955-1977 (Box 13, Folder 7-9)
  - San Diego Fine Arts Festival, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - San Francisco Museum of Art, 1963-1975 (Box 13, Folder 11-12)
  - Sanski Art Center, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Santa Barbara Museum of Art, 1956-1976 (Box 13, Folder 14-15)
  - Schenectady Museum, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Schneider Galleries, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Schoonover Gallery, 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Paul Schuster Art Gallery, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - [Schwartz, Richard], 1979-1983 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Schweitzer Gallery, 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Scotland, 1970s-1980s (Box 13, Folder 22-23)
  - Seattle Art Museum [John LaFarge Window], 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - "A Selective Checklist From the Collections of Graham" [Notated], 1962 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Services, circa 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Sheboygan Foundation, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Shipping, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - E. & A. Silberman Galleries, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - [Sindler, Richard, M.D.], 1981 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Skidmore College, 1959-1970 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Skidmore, Owings & Merrill, 1963-1968 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Smith College, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Smithsonian Institute, 1968-1977 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - The Society of the Four Arts, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Sotheby's, 1963-1964; 1976 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - South Dakota Memorial Art Center, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Southern Methodist University, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Southern Vermont Art, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - [Sowell, Anne], 1983 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Spark, Victor, 1954-1984 (Box 13, Folder 41-44)
  - Spark, Victor, Inventory, 1960s (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Spark, Victor, Nude and Drapery [Exhibition?], 1973 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - St. Cloud State College, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - State Historical Society of Missouri, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - State University of New York, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Steuben Glass, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Stolen Artwork From Robin's Office (Feb. 1986), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - [Stolen Artwork From Robin's Office], George Henry Durrie, circa 1986 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - [Stolen Artwork From Robin's Office], Cornelius Krieghoff, circa 1986 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Stolen Objects, 1984-1992 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Stolen Paintings, 1985-1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - [Stoll, Leo], 1979-1982 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Storage, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Sugarman v. Duveen Legal File, 1957-1958 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Summer Festival, 1955 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Syracuse Museum, 1975; 1957-1959 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - T Correspondence, 1963-1983 (Box 14, Folder 14-16)
  - [T-U Correspondence], circa 1978-1984 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - T General, 1955-1977 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Taxes, 1965-1968 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Third Floor Exhibitions Prior to 1974, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Three Two Seven Gallery, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Tokyo National Museum, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Toldeo Museum of Art, 1969; 1956-1957 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Tower Gallery, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Travel File, circa 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Trinity University Press, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Trosby Gallery, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Tuscon Art Center, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - U Correspondence, 1955-1985 (Box 14, Folder 29-32)
  - U General, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - United States Department of the Interior, 1969-1976 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Universal Limited Art Editions, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - University of Arizona, 1967; 1975 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - University of California, 1969; 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - University of California, Berkeley, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - University of Cincinnati, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - University of Connecticut, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - University of Delaware, 1973-1975 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - University of Illinois, 1956-1966 (Box 14, Folder 42-43)
  - University of Iowa, 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - University of Kansas, 1973-1977 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - University of Maine, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - University of Maryland, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - University of Nebraska, 1956-1977 (Box 14, Folder 48-49)
  - University of Notre Dame, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - University of Southern Illinois, 1966-1967 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - University of St. Thomas, 1962-1963 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - University of Texas, 1975; 1965-1969 (Box 14, Folder 54-55)
  - University of Utah, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - V Correspondence, 1962-1983 (Box 14, Folder 57-60)
  - V General, 1974; 1955-1962 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Vassar College, 1969; 1967 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Vatican [Empty Folder], undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Venice Biennale, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1958-1961 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Visual Arts Gallery, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - W Bills, 1955-1965 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - W Correspondence, 1961-1983 (Box 15, Folder 8-12)
  - W General, 1967-1977; 1954-1963 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Wadsworth Atheneum, 1980-1990; 1958-1967 (Box 15, Folder 14-16)
  - Wake Forest University, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Walker Art Center, 1956-1968; 1976 (Box 15, Folder 18-20)
  - [Warner Collection], 1981 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Washburn Gallery, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Washington Gallery of Art, 1962-1966 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Wayne State University, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - [Weeks, Edward], 1979 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - [Weingeroff Enterprises, Inc.], 1981-1983 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Weiss, Morris, 1974-1976 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - The Western Association of Art Museum Directors, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Westminster College, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - The White House, Washington, D.C., 1974-1978 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1955-1980 (Box 15, Folder 31-33)
  - [Wilbur, Brayton, Jr.], 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - The Wilmington Society of the Fine Arts, 1967-1969 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Winterthur Museum, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Woodward Foundation, 1962-1966 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Works of Art at the Framers/Restorers, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Sheridan, Wyoming, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - X-Y-Z Bills, 1955-1963 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - X-Y-Z Correspondence, 1977-1983 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - X-Y-Z General, 1955-1977 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Y Correspondence, 1990; 1963-1975 (Box 15, Folder 43-44)
  - [Y-Z Correspondence], circa 1978-1984 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Yale University, 1963-1966 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Yale University Art Gallery, 1960-1981 (Box 15, Folder 47-48)
  - Young Art Dealers Association, 1997-1999 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Z Correspondence, 1968; 1963 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Zabriski Gallery, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Zadok, Charles, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 52)
- Exhibition Files, 1947-2004; 1912; Series 2; 8 Linear feet Boxes 16-24
  Exhibition Files documents the gallery's exhibitions through catalogs, clippings, correspondence, guest books, notes, photographs, press materials, price lists, and scattered sales receipts and other financial records. Materials found here only provide partial documentation of the gallery's exhibition schedule. Exhibitions at the gallery from the 1980s-1990s are especially under-represented.
  In addition to James Graham & Sons, this series includes exhibitions held by Duveen-Graham Gallery, Graham Gallery, Graham Modern, and JG|Contemporary, as well as Graham's participation in art fairs (late 1980s-1990s). Additional exhibition materials are also found in other series.
  Originally, much of the material was arranged by subject, such as British pottery shows or Illustration exhibitions. However, the series has been rearranged chronologically according to exhibition date. Guest books are arranged at the end of the series.
  - Aspects Exhibition, 1954-1962 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - "New Talent in the USA" (Feb. 15 - Mar. 8, 1955) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - "An Exhibition of Contemporary American Indian Painters" (Oct. 15 - Nov. 15, 1955), 1947-1956 (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
  - Fulbright Artists (Sept. 25 - Oct. 13, 1956), 1956-1957 (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
  - "The Classical Art of Negro Africa" (Nov. 26 - Dec. 14, 1957), 1955-1958 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - [Japanese Artists], 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Japanese Group Show (June 16 - July 31, 1958), 1957-1958 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - "Contemporary Painting From India" (Feb. 10-26, 1959), 1958-1961 (Box 16, Folder 10-11)
  - "Architectural Ideas I & II: Norman Bluhm and Elaine De Kooning", circa 1960s (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - New York Show, 1960s-1970s (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - "Post-Mondrian Abstraction in America" [Empty Folder], circa 1960s (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - "The 50th Anniversary of the Exhibition of Independent Artists in 1910" (Jan. 9 - Feb. 21, 1960), circa 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 15-16)
  - Three Dutch Artists (Apr. 12 - May 7, 1960), 1957-1960 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - "Romantic Painting" (Apr. 21 - May 19, 1961), 1912; 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Western Exhibition - American Indian Paintings and Sculpture (1962), 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - "Abstract Inflationism," Eva Hesse, Jean Linder, Paul Harris, Frank Viner, Mark Morell (1966), 1978; 1964-1966 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - John La Farge Exhibition (1966), 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - "Art: Authentic and Fake" Benefit for Big Brothers (May 1-20, 1967) (Box 16, Folder 22-23)
  - 110th Anniversary Exhibition (Sept. 20 - Oct. 18, 1967) (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - "Birds and Beasts" (Jan. 1969), 1949; 1982; 1963-1969 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - "Mom, Apple Pie and the American Flag" (Jan. 7 - Feb. 1, 1969) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Flower Still Life Exhibition (Mar. 1-29, 1969) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - "The Big Drawing" (Apr. 8 - May 3, 1969) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Historical Steam Engines Show (1970), 1965-1970 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - "Birds and Beasts" (Feb. 7 - Mar. 5, 1970), 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Lettick, Birney (Sept. 15 - Oct. 10, 1970), 1970-1972 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - "Cartoon and Comic Strip Arts" (Apr. 4-29, 1972), 1972-1976 (Box 17, Folder 9-12)
  - Wildlife Conservation International Exhibition (May 2-9, 1972), 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - "Contemporary North American Ornithological Painters" (Nov. - Dec. 1972), 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 14-15)
  - "Links, Now & Then" Exhibition (1973), 1969; 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - "English Illustrations of the 19th and 20th Centuries" (Nov. 6 - Dec. 1, 1973), 1972-1983 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - English Shows and W.C. [Watercolors?], 1974-1979 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - "Flowers: Contemporary American" (Mar. 26 - Apr. 20, 1974) (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - "19th and 20th Century Nautical Paintings" Exhibition (Apr. 1974), 1968 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Drawing Show (June 1974), 1974-1975; 1981 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - American Scottish Artists Exhibition, 1975; 1978 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - "19th and 20th Century American Sporting Scenes in Bronze and Oil" (Oct. 29 - Dec. 6, 1975) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Salmagundi Club, circa 1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Occult [1976?], circa 1976 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - "American Cartoons, Comics and Illustrations" (Jan. 31 - Feb. 29, 1976), circa 1972-1979 (Box 18, Folder 6-8)
  - Summer Group Show (1976) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - "The Art of Pastel" (1977) (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Haitian Paintings (circa 1977), 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Stained Glass Exhibition [1977?], 1973-1978 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Hoffman, Malvina (Jan. - Apr. 1977), 1976 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - "24 British Potters," Pennsylvania State University Traveling Show (Jan. 5-29, 1977), 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - "A Separate Reality" (Symbolism) (May 10 - June 17, 1977), 1947-1978 (Box 18, Folder 15-16)
  - "Four Masters of Narrative Art" (June 21 - July 29, 1977), 1974-1978 (Box 18, Folder 17-18)
  - Exhibition (Sept. 1977), 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - "British Pottery '77" (Dec. 7, 1977 - Jan. 21, 1978), 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 20-24)
  - "Toward Abstraction: Arthur B. Davies, Oscar F. Bluemner, Helen Torr and others" (Jan. - Feb. 1978), 1977-1978; 1972 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - "F.R. Gruger and His Circle" (Nov. 2-22, [1978?]), 1965; 1973-1983 (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
  - "British Pottery '78" (Dec 2-23, 1978), 1977-1979 (Box 19, Folder 4-7)
  - British Pottery, Correspondence (1979), 1976-1980 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - "Christmas 1979", 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Fantastic Illus. Show and Material, circa 1980 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - "Originals" (Jan. 15 - Feb. 20, 1980), 1979-1981 (Box 19, Folder 11-12)
  - "Symbolist and Imaginative Paintings" (June - Aug. 8, 1980), 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - "In the Geometric Tradition: Fritz Glarner, Carl Holty, Albert Swinden" (Sept. 23 - Oct. 25, 1980), 1979-1983; circa 1956; 1973 (Box 19, Folder 14-16)
  - "British Pottery '80," Geoffrey Swindell (Dec. 2, 1980 - Jan. 9, 1981), 1978-1982 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - "American Illustrations, 1892-1980" (Dec. 16, 1980 - Jan. 24, 1981), 1978-1981 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - "Great American Illustrations (Apr. 28 - May 24, 1981) (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - "Mark Adams: Recent Watercolors" (Nov. 7 - Dec. 5, 1981), 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - "British Pottery '81" (Dec. 2, 1981 - Jan. 9, 1982), 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - "British Pottery '81" (Dec. 2, 1981 - Jan. 9, 1982), 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 1-4)